gearculture.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy Statement | GearCulture

GearCulture respects the privacy of its visitors and is committed to protecting its visitors’ personal information. This Privacy Statement covers the site www.gearculture.com. We collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit our web site unless you choose to provide that information to us or as specifically outlined in this Policy.

####  Email Addresses

If you entrust us with your email address at anytime, we guarantee that we will not share it or any other personal contact information you provide with any third party.

We do not currently send advertising via email, but if we do so in the future, we will remove you from any mailing list upon your request. If you wish to remove your email address from any future mailing, you may do so by contacting us directly via our contact form.

#### Cookies

Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you view or click on their advertisements. Cookies are used to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. GearCulture does not have access to this data and will not use it for future marketing efforts. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie. This will give you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

#### Links

Our Web site provides links to other web sites, sites that may be maintained by companies that are not affiliates of ours. GearCulture is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites and we encourage you to use caution. In particular, we recommend that you view the privacy policy posted on each site to confirm the sites policies are acceptable to you. This Policy applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

#### Traffic Report

The basic user information collected is used to help us analyze web traffic, improve the content of our web site and your experience on our web site.

GearCulture’s analytics software collects industry-standard traffic reporting records, IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages. We use aggregate forms of this information to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to determine the popularity of specific features.

#### Third-Party Advertising Companies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.gearculture.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/03/opt_out.asp).

#### Changes to Our Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here.
